fortunebuilders.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy Policy - FortuneBuilders

## FortuneBuilders.com Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. In order to demonstrate our firm commitment to full transparency and best business practices, we have developed the following Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy sets forth the policy of FortuneBuilders, Inc. (together with its subsidiaries, “the Company,” “us,” “we,” or “our”) concerning the collection, handling and storage of user information collected through the use of FortuneBuilders.com and/or any other related website that links to this Privacy Policy (the “Website”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how we process your information. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 10/5/2015. 

### Personal Information

Information We May Collect. Depending on the circumstances, we may collect and hold a range of different information about you, including, but not limited to, name and contact information or billing information (“Personal Information”). What kind of information we collect may depend on whether you are a visitor to the Website (“Visitors”), or have purchased a product or service and/or paid a monthly fee to subscribe to our services (“Members”). For example, Members who register to use our services will be asked to provide Personal Information such as name, address, telephone number, email address and billing information (such as a credit card number and billing address). 

How We Collect Personal Information. The Company collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members, including when you provide information to us when you resister for an event, fill out a survey, purchase a product or service, create an account, register for a service, subscribe to our newsletters or catalogs, or contact us with an inquiry or request. We reserve the right to combine Personal Information collected from the Website with any other information we collect.

How We May Use Personal Information. We may use Personal Information:

To present the Website to you and others, including the content, features, applications and functionalities made available via the Website.

To facilitate registration for our services. The Personal Information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member’s account (such as for billing purposes). 

To facilitate the purchase of our products and services. If you order services or products directly from the Company, we will use the Personal Information you provide to process that order. 

To provide Members with notices about your accounts and to communicate with you regarding the availability of the Website, security and other Website-related issues, and to send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Website and changes to our terms, conditions and policies. 

To respond to email inquiries. When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to us, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive.

To conduct analysis, research and development for the improvement of the Website and our products and services, to provide you and others with improved services, and to customize your experience with the Website and services. 

For our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new websites, products and services, enhancing, improving or modifying our services, identifying usage trends, conducting studies and analyzing the results of studies, and operating and expanding our business activities. 

If we reasonably believe it is necessary or appropriate: (i) under applicable law; (ii) to comply with legal process; (iii) to respond to requests from public and government authorities; (iv) to enforce our terms and conditions; (v) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (vi) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; or (vii) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

In any other way we may describe to you when you provide the Personal Information. 

How Personal Information May Be Disclosed

To our employees, affiliates, or third parties who provide services to us, including service providers and contractors that assist us with the purposes for which we use your Personal Information. In instances where the Company and a partner jointly promote services, we may provide the partner certain Personal Information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. 

Some products and services may be offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contractor seller, or non-affiliated partner, including those providing real estate investment software and business services. To provide Visitors and Members some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain Personal Information. 

To third parties to facilitate or implement a transfer/sale of all or part of our assets or business, or in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

If we reasonably believe it is necessary or appropriate: (i) under applicable law; (ii) to comply with legal process; (iii) to respond to requests from public and government authorities; (iv) to enforce our terms and conditions; (v) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (vi) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; or (vii) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

In any other way we may describe to you when you provide the Personal Information. 

### Unsubscribing from Email Communication

You can unsubscribe from email communication at any time using the link provided at the bottom of all our emails or by emailing [support@fortunebuilders.com](mailto:support@fortunebuilders.com).

### Other Information

Other Information We May Collect: “Other Information” is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an identifiable individuals, such as: browser and device information; Internet Protocol (“IP”) address; pages visited; average time spent on the Website; information collected through cookies and other technologies; and aggregated information. 

How We May Collect Other Information. We may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including:

Through your use of the Website. When you visit the Website, we may track and collect Website usage data, such as your search history.

Through cookies and other technologies. A “cookie” is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. The Company may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Visitor or Member we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. To learn more about cookies, including information on what cookies have been set on your computer and how cookies can be managed and deleted, visit <https://www.ftc.gov/site-information/privacy-policy/internet-cookies>. 

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. We also use tracking pixels (i.e. Google Analytics) to aid in measuring and tracking where our website traffic is coming from and to track the performance of our site. Finally, we use remarking pixels from Facebook and Google to aid in customized, targeted followup advertising.

IP Address. Your IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses the Website, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We may use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels of the Website, helping diagnose server problems, and administering the Website and its associated services.

From you. Information, such as your preferred means of communication, is collected when you voluntarily provide this information.

By aggregating information. Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Website. 

How We May Use and Disclose Other Information.

We may use and disclose Other Information for any lawful purpose, such as for research, reporting and analytic purposes and to improve the Website. 

The company may share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and Members collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with advertisers. Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements or joint ventures. Additionally, our partners may have advertisements or co-branded Web Pages that are cosponsored by an affiliate, independent contractor seller, or non-affiliated partner. We may share non-identifying and aggregate information with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services offered.

If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use it for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information.

In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information (such as by combining non-identifying information such as a user’s state with the user’s name). If we combine any Other Information and Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information as long as it is combined. 

### Third Party Services

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including our other Website users or any third party operating any site or service to which the Website links to or is linked from. The inclusion of a link on the Website does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us or our affiliates.

### Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our Website.

### Use of Services By Minors

This Website is not intended for the use of individuals under the age of 18, and we request that these individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Website or any associated services. The Company does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from individuals under 18 years of age. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, or you have any privacy related concerns, please contact us via:

FortuneBuilders, Inc. Attn: Compliance Department  
3033 Bunker Hill St.  
San Diego, CA, 92109  
Tel: 619-881-0575  
Fax: 888-506-9279  
Email: support@fortunebuilders.com 

If you are a California resident, you are entitled to request, once a year, what information, if any, we shared with other businesses and for what purpose. Please request this information by contacting us by email at support@fortunebuilders.com.

Please note that email communications are not always secure; please do not include sensitive information in your emails to us.

### Do Not Track Disclosure

As we do not track the activity of our users across third-party websites, we do not respond to “Do Not Track” signals. 

### Updates to This Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy by notifying you of such changes by any reasonable means, including by posting a revised Privacy Policy on the Website.

Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. The “last updated” date above indicates when this Privacy Policy was last changed.
